I’ve been all alone
I guess I’m all alone like an island in the crowd
사람들 속에서도 나 혼자 섬인가 봐
No matter how hard I try, I just feel it’s empty
아무리 채워봐도 텅 빈 것만 같아
Everywhere I go, I’m wildly looking for
Everywhere I go 난 미친 것처럼 끝없이
something without end
뭔가를 찾아 헤매
I think I’ve had enough don’t wanna be alone
Where are you I need you
Don’t say it’s an accident
우연이라 하지 마
Without you, everything’s a lie
Why did you show up now
왜 이제 나타난 거야
I’m like hello hello hello
Where you’ve been all my life
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Hello hello hello
Where you’ve been all my life
I don’t wanna go back
All alone in loneliness
홀로 외로움 속에
Please say it to me
어서 내게 건네줘
Tell me hello again
Fizzled out, and the hollow
흐지부지 구렁텅이
Draw the rainbow of life
삶의 무지개를 피고
Pass by the dark that rain has left
비가 떠난 어둠이 지나 너란
Get into the morning called you
아침의 품으로
After spending my past where I rode a lonely wave at every moment
매 순간 감정의 파도를 외롭게 탔었던
그런 나란 놈을 보내고 말해 안녕 또 안녕
Say hello and hello
Goodbye my tears
내 눈물아 안녕
Goodbye loneliness
쓸쓸함도 안녕
Now my heart starts beating, it’s like pump pump
자 이제 뛰기 시작해 심장 소리는 Pump pump
Don’t say it’s an accident
우연이라 하지 마
Without you, everything’s a lie
Why did you show up now
왜 이제 나타난 거야
I’m like hello hello hello
Where you’ve been all my life
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Hello hello hello
Where you’ve been all my life
Whoa oh oh oh oh oh like a miracle
Whoa oh oh oh oh oh 기적처럼
If I meet you
널 만난다면
I don’t mind being burned I’ve been waiting
불타도 좋아 난 기다렸어
I want the love that beats my heart
원해 가슴 뛰는 Love 목숨 걸 수 있는 Girl
A girl I can risk my life for
1, 2, 3, 4 You know what I’m waiting for
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na
Yeah I’m lookin’ I’m lookin’ I’m lookin’ for you
Yeah I’m lookin' I’m lookin’ I’m lookin’ for you
Hello hello hello
Where you’ve been all my life